Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/eduardo-david-barba (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Software Development
.NET Core
Web Services

Certifications

Microsoft Certified Professional

Microsoft® Certified Technology Specialist: .NET Framework 3.5, ASP.NET Applications

Microsoft® Certified Technology Specialist: .NET Framework 4, Data Access

Eduardo Barba

MS Backend Developer

Quito Canton, Pichincha, Ecuador

Summary

+12 years overall experience as .NET Backend Software Engineer. Strong experience in the design and development of solutions for API services, web applications.

Good attitude for taking initiative, team-working, and making decisions.

Resilience and quick adapting to work with new technologies and different development environments.

Optimistic and eager to learn and apply new technologies and knowledge.

Experience

EPAM Systems Senior Software Engineering May 2022 - Present (4 months)

ThoughtWorks
Senior Consultant Developer
September 2017 - May 2022 (4 years 9 months)
Ecuador

MS Backend developer

SAFI ERP - Herrera Carvajal y Asociados Cia. Ltda. Freelance Developer
October 2015 - September 2017 (2 years)
Quito, Ecuador

Herrera Carvajal (SAFI)

SkyPostal
Freelance Developer
March 2015 - May 2015 (3 months)
Quito, Pichincha, Ecuador

nDeveloper Cía. Ltda.

Senior Developer January 2011 - February 2015 (4 years 2 months) Quito, Ecuador

ESDINAMICO

Freelance Developer December 2009 - November 2010 (1 year) Quito, Pichincha, Ecuador

TATA Consultancy Services IT Analyst January 2008 - April 2009 (1 year 4 months) Quito, Pichincha, Ecuador

Banco Pichincha

Education

Universidad Tecnológica Equinoccial
INGENIERO EN INFORMATICA Y CIENCIAS DE LA
COMPUTACION, Computer Software Engineering · (2001 - 2007)

Universidad Técnica Particular de Loja
DIPLOMA SUPERIOR EN GESTION DE FINANZAS, Accounting and
Finance · (May 2009 - November 2009)